MIGUEL A. CAMACHO

1401-626-2067 mcamacho1990@icloud. com

15 Roma Street, apt 3 Bristol, RI 02809

Profile

Highly motivated CompTia A+ certified computer technician. Experienced in PC repair, trouble shooting via networking and operating systems, mobile devices ,and security. Great understanding of MAC OS, Linux, Mobile OS and Windows. Proficient in connecting users to the data they need to do their jobs regardless of the devices being used. Currently completing a course with the Code Institute of Technology, capitalizing on skills in front and back-end web development utilizing JavaScript Libraries and Frameworks. I'm looking forward to utilizing my skill set in order to lead a team in developing, maintaining, and providing technological support for an information system structure for a start up company.

Experience

Certified Medical Technician- Silver Creek Manor; Bristol, RI — 2017-Present Managing 120 patients medications in a sub-acute skilled nursing facility. Working closely as a member of an interdisciplinary team to ensure optimum patient outcomes. Accessing and documenting information in EHR and EMAR through Matrix Care . Electronically ordering patients medications. Stocking supplies and medications. Assessing patients needs for medication gradual dose increase/reduction. Responsible for accurate medication administration and documentation. In charge of overseeing and training newly licensed/hired CMT's.

Certified Nursing Assistant- Silver Creek Manor; Bristol, RI- 2014-Present Assisting in ADL care. Working with an interdisciplinary team in a medical facility to ensure patient safety and positive outcomes. Accessing and documenting information in EHR through POC electronic charts. Maintaining infection control standards and prevention during patient care. Responsible for overseeing and training newly licensed/hired CNA's..

MedFx Warwick, RI - 2013-2014

Software engineer. Maintaining and updating medical software program systems in an agile based team. Attending and participating in daily scrub meetings to ensure employee cohesiveness in maintaining optimal software for users. Setting and attaining set team goals. Overseeing fluidity of software operations.

Education

Computer Technician- CompTIA A+ ID_COMP001021095679 New Horizons Computer Learning Center

Certified Medication Technician- CMT ID_MAD02445 Roger Williams University

Certified Nursing Assistant- CNA ID_NA40862 Aquidneck Island Learning Center

References

Upon Request.